Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Das froehliche Standchen Uniform Title: Froehliche Standchen, undated (Box 162, Folder 2680)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Das treue deutsche Herz Uniform Title: Treue deutsche Herz, undated (Box 110, Folder 1579)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Des Abends Uniform Title: Des Abends, undated (Box 155, Folder 2416)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Die Dorfmusik Uniform Title: Dorfmusik, undated (Box 80, Folder 1026)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Die Lust'ge Band Uniform Title: Lust'ge Band, undated, undated (Box 165, Folder 2797)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Ecce quam bonum Uniform Title: Ecce quam bonum Publisher information: New York: Deutscher Liederkranz, undated (Box 113, Folder 1614)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Einer von unsere Leut. Selections Uniform Title: Einer von unsere Leut. Selections, undated (Box 116, Folder 1651)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Five Favorite Yule-Tide Songs Uniform Title: Five Favorite Yule-Tide Songs Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 15068-17 1/2, undated (Box 127, Folder 1854)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Grablied Uniform Title: Grablied, undated (Box 160, Folder 2601)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Hinaus auf die Sie! Uniform Title: Hinaus auf die Sie!, undated (Box 162, Folder 2667)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Hoch! Uniform Title: Hoch!, undated (Box 163, Folder 2713)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Horch, was kommt Uniform Title: Horch, was kommt, undated (Box 161, Folder 2654)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: L. K. Sangerspruch Uniform Title: L. K. Sangerspruch, undated (Box 170, Folder 3018)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Look for the silver lining Uniform Title: Look for the silver lining, undated (Box 165, Folder 2810)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: March Along Uniform Title: March Along, undated (Box 167, Folder 2869)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Nun danket all Gott; Eine feste Burg Uniform Title: Nun danket alle Gott; Ein feste Burg Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 1275, undated (Box 156, Folder 2469)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: O du frohliche Uniform Title: O du frohliche, undated (Box 127, Folder 1835)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: O komm, mein Kind, zum Wald hinein! Uniform Title: O komm, mein Kind, zum Wald hinein! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.249., undated (Box 168, Folder 2920)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: O Tannenbaum Uniform Title: O Tannenbaum, undated (Box 115, Folder 1646)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Puer natus Uniform Title: Puer natus Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated (Box 151, Folder 2236)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Regenhusch Uniform Title: Regenhusch, undated (Box 127, Folder 1861)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Sanctus Uniform Title: Sanctus, undated (Box 115, Folder 1642)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Tell me where is Fancy bred? Uniform Title: Tell me where is Fancy bred?, undated (Box 162, Folder 2695)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: The star spangled banner Uniform Title: Star spangled banner, undated (Box 150, Folder 2184)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Veteranen Fest Uniform Title: Veteranen Fest, undated (Box 80, Folder 1027)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Waldabendschein Uniform Title: Waldabendschein Publisher information: New York, undated (Box 117, Folder 1677)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Wehmuts Lieder Uniform Title: Wehmuts Lieder, undated (Box 80, Folder 1029)
  - Composer: [n/a] Title: Weihnachtsglocken Uniform Title: Weihnachtsglocken, undated (Box 115, Folder 1647)
- Oversize Series IC: Music, Choral
  - "Deutsche Volkslieder," orchestrated by Papageno for the 1963 Charity Concert, orchestra and chorus, score, manuscript (Box IC.1, Folder 94A)
  - Liszt, Franz, "Missa Solemnis," score, probably 1st ed., 1859 (Box IC.2, Folder 53A)
- Oversize Series IIA: Liederkranz Library Documents / Materials
  - Liederkranz Music Library's Card Catalog, undated (Box IIA.3, Folder 195A)
  - "Season of 1924-1925, Seating of Orchestra, Rehearsal Room, Scale ½" = 1'0"," seating map, two copies, found folded in large library ledger (folder 203), 1924-09-24 (Folder 3 Left)